Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
So that's the largest magical city
in the northern lands, Äußerst.
We're still a long ways away.
We'll need to hitch a ride on
a carriage on our way there.
Once you get your first-class
mage certification there,
we'll be able to enter the Northern Plateau.
I don't think I have to be
the one to get certified.
I won't be able to use it for long, anyway.
You should get certified, Fern.
Ms. Frieren, don't you know?
Only a handful of the most skilled mages
have ever gained a first-class certification.
I certainly couldn't manage it.
Oh, really?
You don't seem interested.
It's a bit late to ask,
but why do we need to be accompanied
by a crazy-powerful mage to enter
the Northern Plateau, anyway?
The Northern Plateau has long been inhabited
by many cunning, magic-using
monsters like the Einsam.
It's a dangerous region that you once couldn't
cross without a priest and a skilled mage.
That said, if someone as valuable
as a skilled mage is required
to travel through the area,
something pretty serious must be
happening on the Northern Plateau.
We'll look into the exam
once we arrive in Äußerst.
According to Fern, there's a combat test.
I'll need to come up with a strategy.
Aren't you powerful enough to
easily handle any kind of test?
Even when you're suppressing your mana,
you still produce as much
as an experienced old mage.
Don't call me an old mage.
Now she's sulking.
Don't you think calling her
an old mage was a bit mean?
I'm sorry.
I haven't forgotten that you
called me an old hag, Stark.
How long ago was that?
Forget it. I'm going to sleep.
Wake me when we get to Äußerst.
Sheesh.
Actually, never mind.
What's wrong?
I could only see half the sky.
What?
Just so you know, Fern,
mana isn't the only factor that
determines a mage's strength.
Technique, experience, the spells
they use, their control...
There's effort and tenacity, too.
Some of those sound more like warrior traits.
Finally, there's talent.
In my life, I've lost eleven times to
mages who had less mana than me.
Four of them were demons.
Qual was one of them.
One was an elf like me,
and the remaining six were humans.
The graf's city should be
coming into view soon.
The road to Äußerst is steep.
Maybe I'll take a break.
That's a nice staff you've got there, miss.
What's this? More bandits?
We're finally enjoying peace now
that Aura has been defeated, too.
But now we're seeing more of these types.
Who told you to speak?
Gather your things and—
Bastard.
If you value your lives,
then leave this place.
Let's go.
Thanks for saving me.
I'm Übel the Mage.
Kraft the Monk.
Huh? Are you an elf?
How unusual. This is my
first time seeing one.
You have the eyes of a killer.
I didn't rescue you.
I found the torn-up bodies
of bandits in the woods nearby.
They'd been killed by a mage.
A tremendously skilled one, no less.
Oh, yeah?
Did you come to lecture me?
No. I'm an adventurer, too.
I'm not so hard-headed as to criticize
someone for killing in self-defense.
I was simply saving the lives
I saw in front of me.
You're a shrewd old man. You're no fun.
Are you headed to Äußerst?
Yeah. I'm going to take
the first-class mage exam.
Frieren said the same thing.
I look forward to hearing about her
adventures when I see her next.
The exam will take place
two months from now.
Keep in mind that the first-class mage exam
is administered once every three years.
Also, a fifth-class mage or higher
certification is required to take the exam.
Fern, it's all up to you.
Ms. Frieren, I can't do this alone.
Sure you can.
What are we going to do if I fail?
The first-class mage exam is only
held once every three years.
We'll either hire a first-class mage
or travel by sea.
That would be incredibly expensive.
We won't be able to afford snacks anymore.
But I'm uncertified.
My holy emblem won't work, will it?
Again, what is that antique?
Hey, you.
Could I take a look at that?
Are you planning to take
the first-class mage exam?
Looks like I get to take the exam.
I'm surprised there's anyone around
who still knows what this is.
Is that thing impressive?
It's supposed to be.
Frieren, you're not part
of a magic guild, are you?
The organizations that manage
magic change all the time.
I can't be bothered to join every one.
Huh.
Besides, I have this.
A holy emblem. Pretty impressive, right?
What's this rusty necklace? Any clue?
None at all.
I see.
But this is the only thing
that proves I'm a mage.
Frieren, it's true that we
don't recognize that necklace.
But we know you're an incredible mage.
Isn't that enough?
But you'll die so soon.
Ms. Frieren.
We know you're an incredible mage.
You're right.
According to the Continental
Magic Association's regulations,
a person becomes a proper mage
once they've achieved at least fifth class.
Fern, why did you get a
third-class certification?
Because it had the soonest
available testing date.
There are 600 mages who
are at least fifth class.
Even when you include apprentices from sixth
to ninth class, there are 2,000 mages total.
Among them, 45 are first class.
The first-class exam is held
once every three years
at the northern branch in Äußerst and the
headquarters in the holy city of Strahl.
Many years, no one passes the test at all.
Some test-takers are expected
to be injured or die.
It seems moderately challenging.
Either way, there are a lot
fewer mages these days.
There used to be more?
A century ago, when the Demon King's
attacks intensified,
you could expect to encounter at least
one mage while walking around town.
These days, you hardly see
them outside magic cities.
Let's train thoroughly to prepare
for the exam in two months.
The first-class mage exam will now begin.
The first-class mage
certification is granted only
This year's test-takers
seem rather exceptional.
Wirbel, second-class mage and
captain of the Northern Magic Corps
to the most exceptionally
talented and powerful mages.
Only a few mages are granted the title.
that has fought against the remnants
of the Demon King's forces for years.
Naturally, the exam is quite dangerous,
Denken, the crafty old
second-class mage who won
but the Association will not intervene
regardless of what happens to you.
a bloody struggle for power
to become an imperial mage.
Fern, the youngest mage to ever receive
a third-class certification with top marks.
Of course, there are some
problem children as well.
Übel, the third-class mage who failed
the second-class exam two years ago
when she killed the first-class mage
who proctored it.
Who else looks promising?
I see someone radiating the mana
of an experienced old mage.
Who is that?
I don't know.
I will now announce the content
of the first test in this exam.
You will be tested as parties.
The 57 exam-takers will split into teams
of three for the first test.
We will now assign parties.
Bracelets, huh?
They have numbers on them.
I must be in the 2nd party.
Imbuing it with mana allows me to locate
the bracelets belonging to my party members.
So this is how we identify
our party members.
Either way, this is interesting.
Setting aside normal party compositions,
these improvised parties of magical
miscreants will struggle to work together.
First impressions are important here.
I should be careful not to make waves.
I sense my party members'
bracelets around here.
Ow, ow, ow!
You're gonna rip them off!
You can't be serious! I'll kill you!
Try it.
They're already fighting.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
Allow me to explain the specific
rules of the first test.
Small birds known as Stille
live within the testing area.
Each party has been given one cage.
There are two conditions you must
fulfill to pass the first test.
First, by sunset tomorrow,
have a cage containing a Stille,
Stay away from me!
and second, have all of your party
members present at that time.
You are mostly free to do as you wish,
but if anyone leaves the testing area,
their entire party will fail the test.
They say that like there isn't a barrier
around the testing area
that won't let so much as
a speck of dust through.
It's not like we can get out.
So they're actually listening
to the explanation.
The first test begins now.
We should start by coming up with a plan!
Are you stupid?
We can't come up with a plan
if we can't even find them!
They're still fighting.
Why don't we introduce
ourselves while we walk?
Also, use rock-paper-scissors to
decide who will carry the cage.
I'm Frieren. Nice to meet you.
I'm Lawine, a third-class mage.
I'm Kanne, also a third-class mage.
Lawine and I go way back.
We graduated from the same magic school.
Do you two know anything about the Stille?
No.
Nope.
I do, but I've never seen
one in person before.
Let's start by finding a
Stille and observing it.
I'm tired.
You're so undisciplined.
Shall we take a break?
I can keep moving. I'll go ahead
and check things out.
It's safer to stay together.
Oh, shut up. That's so inefficient.
Lawine, are you strong?
Stronger than her.
You wanna fight, huh?
And compared to me?
I wouldn't want to fight you.
I see.
Fine. Go check things out.
Come back if it gets too dangerous.
Okay.
And watch the skies.
I know.
I wonder if our party will be okay.
Frieren, you're like a teacher.
You'd make a good leader.
It's because you two keep fighting.
I don't want to lead.
Sorry. We've always been like this.
By the way, what did you mean
when you said to watch the skies?
I meant exactly what I said.
Do you struggle to detect mana?
Why?
Hey.
That was quick.
I found a Stille.
Nicely done, Lawine. Now watch it closely.
I told you to observe.
It's going to run away.
I don't think so. Nice work, Kanne.
Huh. Not bad.
But you should probably get down.
What? Why?
Stille are incredibly tough.
Their top speed is faster
than the speed of sound.
Trying to restrain one
like that is pointless.
Seriously? It's already gone.
That was close.
Capturing one will require
careful observation.
We'll use this entire day
for Stille observation.
Kanne controlled the water,
and Lawine froze it.
Their timing was perfectly coordinated.
Their teamwork is superb.
It's not something you
could achieve overnight.
I was worried for a while there,
but this might actually work.
Let's go after it.
We should search around the lake instead.
Why? We should go sooner rather than later.
Nope. They're fighting again.
I hear something. Huh?
Frieren's missing.
It's faint, but that's the sound of rain.
But it's not raining, so why...?
Oh, I see.
Does that mean...?
A monster!
My staff...
Lawine!
I told you to watch the skies.
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
You called Lawine's name.
But you don't like Lawine, do you?
No, I don't.
Right? So how do you two
work together so well?
It's strange.
I'm surprisingly craven.
I often fail to act during critical moments.
It happened when I cast
my first flying spell, too.
The ones who already left
are already so far away.
You'll have water beneath you,
so it's not like you'll die.
If you don't have the courage
to do it, want me to kick you?
I hate you, Lawine.
I know.
You're always so mean to me.
I'm the kind of person who
grows with praise, you know.
You're joking, right?
This is what happens when you grow up
babied by a kind mommy and daddy.
If it'll help you fly,
I'll be as nice as you want.
Then name my strengths.
Are you for real?
You try really hard even
though you're a coward.
What?
That's your strength.
Tell me more.
What? Why?
You work really hard in secret.
You're considerate and pay attention
to your surroundings.
More.
You're cute when you smile.
What? Ew.
That was close.
So you can fly after all.
I'm done being kind to you.
Lawine is rough, but she
pulls me along with her.
Because of her, I realized
I can manage most things
if I just go for it, even if I'm scared.
By the way, Frieren...
I noticed something interesting.
Do you think this could be useful?
I see.
We might be able to capture
a Stille easily after all.
It's strange.
Let's do this.
Why are you so relaxed?
They're inexperienced.
Someone's detected us.
It's time to fight other mages.
Shut up.
Then there's no need for words.
This is the 2nd party's well-laid plan.